

519 500 8887 t.hackbart@gmail.com 1175 Hackbart Road Wellesley Ontario N0B 2T0 GitHub: tylerhackbart LinkedIn: LinkedIn.com/in/TylerHackbart Portfolio: tylerhackbart.com

## **Applicant Overview**

I am a motivated, responsible front-end developer with a diverse work background who cares deeply about design and user experience. I am excited by companies that are building meaningful products and disruptive technologies. I have a dedicated, farm-raised work ethic coupled with a passion for crafting amazing user interactions.

## Skills

- Proficient in Ruby, Rails framework, jQuery, JavaScript, HTML5/ CSS, Node, Git & GitHub and Object Oriented Design, through educational experience at Bitmaker Labs
- Experience in Objective C and Swift for iOS Platform, Adobe Photoshop and WordPress, through personal interest and projects
- Practical knowledge of how a start up runs, working on different teams of start up companies
- Excellent interpersonal and communication skills resulting for experience in various human service roles

## **Relevant Experience**

WEB DEVELOPER - OCT 2014 - CURRENT

DATE IN A BOX, WATERLOO ONTARIO

- Job entails design and programming both mobile and desktop sites, written with Ruby
- Very early stage of start up, currently working on first version of both the web application and mobile app for the iOS platform

**IOS DEVELOPER - AUG 2014 - CURRENT** 

GRANDEZVOUS . TORONTO ONTARIO

- Designing and programming the GrandezVous application for the iOS platform
- Languages used are Objective C, as well as testing with Swift

FRONT END DEVELOPER INTERN - APR 2014 - AUG 2014

**BLURBI, TORONTO ONTARIO** 

- Converted photoshop mockups of numerous webpages throughout blurbi.ca
- Languages used were HTML, CSS, Bootstrap frameworks, and Node.js

**CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE - JUN 2013 - CURRENT** 

STAPLES CANADA, WATERLOO ONTARIO

- Expanded to all available positions early on, originally hired as technology sales
- Occasional technical work; setting up the personal interface for customer computers, running virus scans and data wipes of units

LINE & PREPARATION COOK - APR 2010 - CURRENT

HARVEST MOON RESTAURANT, ST. JACOBS ONTARIO

- Food preparation in fast paced, team environment
- Supervisory responsibilities including ensuring staff's responsibilities are complete, closing day sales, final checks of building and executing closing procedure.

## Education

Bitmaker Labs, Toronto Ontario – 9 Week Immersive Web Developer - 2014

Elmira Secondary High School, Elmira Ontario – Diploma – 2007 - 2012